// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Data science is the process of diverse set of data through",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "organizing data",
      "processing data",
      "analysing data",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The modern conception of data science as an independent discipline is sometimes attriutes to",
    answer: "Willian S.",
    options: [
      "Willian S.",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Arthur Samuel",
      "Satoshi Nakakmoto"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following language is used in Data Science?",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
      "C",
      "C++",
      "R",
      "Ruby"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is false?",
    answer: "Raw data should be processed only one time",
    options: [
      "Raw data should be processed only one time",
      "Subsetting can be used to select and exclude variables and observations",
      "Merging concerns combining datasets on the same observations to produce a result",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Important skills for a Data Scientist",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "Probability & Statistics",
      "ML & DL",
      "Data Wrangling",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following are correct component for data science",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Data Engineering",
      "Advanced Computing",
      "Domain Expertose",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the followinf is not a part of Data Science process",
    answer: "Communication Building",
    options: [
      "Discovery",
      "Model planning",
      "Communication Building",
      "Operationalize"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following are the Data sources in data science",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "Structured",
      "Unstructured",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Data can be categorized into ______ groups",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "A column is a _______ representation of data",
    answer: "vertical",
    options: [
      "horizontal",
      "diagonal",
      "vertical",
      "top"
    ]
  },

];